# **BOGDAN MIHOCI**

0745 4440 442



bogdanmihoci27@gmail.com







#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a Full Stack Developer with experience in designing, documenting, testing and implementing new, custom applications for commercial use. In my work, my goal is to seamlessly blend the demands of modern business with the world of technology.

As an enthusiastic, passionate and motivated person, I am keen to analyze complex requirements and to develop an in-depth understanding of the company's needs and objectives, by creating solutions that add value and increase efficiency. I pride myself in my ability to build user-friendly interfaces and continuously optimize the code for faster performance. My goal-oriented mindset, prompt troubleshooting and problem-solving skills help me ensure the timely completion of all my projects. I am keen to learn new technologies and new programing languages.

#### **EDUCATION**

**COMPUTING & IT** 

BSc, Open University

2015 - 2021

#### **CERTIFICATES**

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate 2020 – 2023

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack Developer

Agent3 / Mar 2020 – Present

Junior Full Stack Developer

Hatcher Components / Jan 2019 – Apr 2020

#### **PROJECTS**

## Agent3

#### SOSELL

A Web Application and the mobile version written in reactJS and react native with the backend written in golang. I also used new technologies like graphql and grpc.

## Hatcher Components:

#### Quality Management System (QMS)

A software solution that helps the company to easily manage aspects of its quality program. The application is a user-friendly, web-based software application that manages, tracks and reports all the company's non-conformances in real-time. It streamlines the complaint process, from client rejection through investigation, root cause analyses all the way to resolution.

#### • Development Process:

- connected with stakeholders to elicit requirements
- wrote /reviewed product requirements
- wrote /reviewed design documents
- developed the application model and presented to senior management
- wrote/reviewed test cases and test strategy for both frontend and backend
- performed unit test and integration tests
- containerized the application and deployed it to the company's server
- Technologies used:
  - Front End:
    - JavaScript (ES6)
    - HTML, CSS
    - ReactJS (react hooks, redux)
    - Typescript
  - Back End:
    - Java
    - Spring Boot (REST API Framework)
    - Spring Security (authentication and authorization JWT)
    - Database (Hibernate/Spring data JPA + MySQL)
  - · Deployment
    - Docker and Docker Compose

## <u>Live Demo</u> <u>Source code</u>

#### University Dissertation Project:

## My Car Expenses

This is a web app that allows users to log car expenses like fuel consumption and cost, service expenses, maintenance and road tax cost. This way users can have an overview of their car expenses over a period of time but also they can compare their expenses against other user's car makes and models.

- Technologies used:
  - Front End:
    - JavaScript (ES6)

- HTML, CSS
- ReactJS
- Typescript
- · Back End:
  - AWS Serverless Services
    - O Lambda
    - O API Gateway
    - O DynamoDB
    - O Cognito

# **LANGUAGES**

**ENGLISH: Fluent** 

**ROMANIAN: Native** 

## **TECHNOLOGIES**

Java, Golang, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, ReactJS, React Native, My-SQL, GraphQL, GRPC, AWS, Docker Swarm, Git